I just tell us about ICA credential
that's the other stock that's reacting
to its quarterform numbers well ICA
credential life insurance is reacting
positively to the numbers and of course
important reasons for that as well uh on
one hand uh the disappointment has come
on the top line that there has been fair
bit of sluggishness when it comes to the
topline growth the premium growth what
has worked for the stock today are two
things one is how the companies managed
to hold on or in fact improve its margin
performance in the quarter second thing
is with respect to the position
positioning of the stock as well. Let's
look at the numbers a little more
closely. New business premium that has
grown at about 14%, total AP that is
down 3%, it's missed CNBC TV8 poll as
well. Retail AP is down 2%. Uh now this
is the sluggishness that I've been
speaking about as far as the topline
growth is concerned. Let's look at the
margins. The margins have improved by
120 basis points. The margins have come
at about 22.7% versus 21.5% on a
year-on-year basis. Against the poll
also, there's been a fair bit of beat
which has come on the margins at 22.7%
versus poll of
21.8%. This is the first factor which
has worked for how the stock is reacting
today. The second thing as I said
positioning it's not the most expensive
stock in the list of life insurance
companies. Also the stock is down 14% in
the last 3 months. So of course taking
respite from how the company managed its
margin performance though the premium
growth has been slow and positioning
working for the stock today. All right
Hash thanks a lot for that. So that's
about ICICI credential up nearly 3%. We
take a short break on the other side of
securities joins in with some trading
strategies.